question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Spoon theory is a theory, utilizing \"Spoons\" as a metaphor for energy they can use in a day.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Musicals &amp; Theatres",
     "question": "The protagonist\'s names in \'Who\'s Afraid of Virginia Woolf\', George and Martha, were derived from George Washington and his wife.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "History",
     "question": "The Kingdom of Prussia briefly held land in Estonia.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "McCree from Overwatch originally started as a character that was going to appear in a scrapped Starcraft game.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "\"Cube\", \"Cube 2: Hypercube\" and \"Cube Zero\" were directed by the same person.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Politics",
     "question": "George Clinton, Vice President of the United States (1805-1812), is an ancestor of President Bill Clinton.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "The weapon Clint Eastwood uses in \"Dirty Harry\" was a .44 Automag.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Vehicles",
     "question": "The term \"GTO\" was originated by Ferrari?", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "The band STRFKR was also briefly known as Pyramiddd.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "History",
     "question": "The fourth funnel of the RMS Titanic was fake designed to make the ship look more powerful and symmetrical.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "History",
     "question": "Joseph Stalin\'s real name was Ioseb Bessarionis dze Dzugashvili.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Science: Gadgets",
     "question": "During the  early parts of the Vietnam War the M16 had a record for having bad reliability",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "The value of one Calorie is different than the value of one calorie.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "Frederick Banting and John Macleod won a Nobel Prize for their contributions to the scientific fields of quantum mechanics.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "History",
     "question": "During the Winter War, the amount of Soviet Union soliders that died or went missing was five times more than Finland\'s.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
     "question": "Throughout the entirety of \"Dragon Ball Z\", Goku only kills two characters: a miniboss named Yakon and Kid Buu.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Science: Computers",
     "question": "The IBM PC used an Intel 8008 microprocessor clocked at 4.77 MHz and 8 kilobytes of memory.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In \"Call Of Duty: World At War\", the first appearance of the \"PPSH-41\" in \"Zombies\" was in the map \"Der Riese\".",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "Pete Townshend\'s solo album, \"White City: A Novel\", is set in the metropolitan area of Chicago.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In \"The Sims\" series, the most members in a household you can have is 8.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
